<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Apparrandear</string>
    <string name="juegos">Games</string>
    <string name="cocteleria">Mixology</string>
    <string name="opciones">Options</string>
    <string name="idioma">LANGUAGE</string>
    <string name="acerca">About...</string>
    <string name="desarrolladopor">Developed by: The DG Crew</string>
    <string name="ron">RUM</string>
    <string name="equipo">Our Team..</string>
    <string name="desarrollador">Programmers</string>
    <string name="disenador">Designers</string>
    <string name="preparacion">Directions:</string>
    <string name="ingredientes">Ingredients:</string>

    <!--
    *************TEQUILA
    -->
    <string name="ingredientesTequila_Margarita">Tequila 60 ml.\nCointreau 30 ml.\n30 ml lime juice.\nIce.\nSalt for the rim of the glass.
</string>
      <string name="prepararTequila_Margarita">Take the glass and rub the edge with the 3/4 lime juice, immediately after passing the edges of the salt.
Place all ingredients (except salt) in a cocktail shaker with ice.
Shake and serve the drink (which should be salted on its edge)
Garnish with a slice of lemon on the rim
</string>
    <string name="ingredientesTequila_Paloma">1 long glass with salt on the rim.\n100ml tequila blanco.\n1 teaspoon of lime juice.\nGrapefruit Soda.\nIce.</string>
<string name="prepararTequila_Paloma">the ice is placed in the cup, add tequila and lime juice and finish filling with grapefruit soda</string>
    <string name="ingredientesTequila_CharroNegro">1/3 de Tequila.\n1/3 lemon or lime juice.\n1/3 coke soda.</string>
    <string name="prepararTequila_CharroNegro">Spread salt on a plate. Rub the rim of the glass with lime wedge and wipe the salt so that it is covered.
        Mix all ingredients in a shaker with crushed ice and shake vigorously. Strain into the cocktail glass salt and garnish with a slice of lime. </string>
    <string name="ingredientesTequila_BloodyMaria">1.5 oz. tequila.\n
3 oz. tomato juice.\n
a touch of hot sauce to taste.\n
a touch of salt to taste.\n
a touch of pepper to taste.\n
a stick of celery.
</string>
    <string name="prepararTequila_BloodyMaria">In a tall glass with ice mix all ingredients. Garnish with lemon.
Optional: Before serving, frost the glass with salt.</string>
<string name="ingredientesTequila_Sunrise">2 ounces (60 ml) of tequila.\n
5 ounces (175 ml) orange juice (can be replaced by two fresh oranges).\n
A splash of grenadine.\n
ice cubes.\n
A slice of orange and a cherry (to decorate).
</string>
    <string name="prepararTequila_Sunrise">1 Place a few ice cubes in the glass.\n
2 Pour the tequila on ice.\n
3 Pour the orange juice into the glass.\n
4 Pour grenadine into the glass.\n
5 Cut a slice of orange.\n
6. Takes a cherry and dress him a slot in the background. Place the cherry on the glass above the slit.\n
7 Place a stirrer or umbrella and serve.
</string>
    <!--
    ****************WHISKY****************
    -->
    <string name="ingredientesWhisky_OldFashioned">1 sugar cube\n
Angostura.\n
soda.\n
Ice.\n
Whisky 60ml.\n
1 slice of orange.\n
1 slice of lemon.\n
</string>
    <string name="prepararWhisky_OldFashioned">Pour into the glass a stroke of Angostura and the sugar cube and wait two minutes.
Fill the glass of soda
Add the ice and stir to dissolve the sugar cube.
Add the Whisky
Garnish with a cocktail bar, a slice of orange and lemon other
</string>
    <string name="ingredientesWhisky_WardEight">• 1½ ounces of bourbon whiskey.\nJuice of half a lemon.\n½ ounce of grenadine.\nSoda
</string>
    <string name="prepararWhisky_WardEight">Shake all ingredients except soda with crushed ice.
Pour, unstrained, in a tall glass. Fill the glass with soda.
If desired, garnish with a slice of fruit.</string>
    <string name="ingredientesWhisky_NightCap">2 oz. whiskey.\n1/2 oz. milk.\n1/2 oz. cocoa cream
</string>
    <string name="prepararWhisky_NightCap">In a shaker with ice, combine all ingredients. Serve in a cocktail glass.</string>
    <string name="ingredientesWhisky_BlackJack">1 1/2 onz whiskey.\n1 kahlúa.\n1/2 triple sec.\n1/2 lemon juice
</string>
    <string name="prepararWhisky_BlackJack">In a blender with ice, combine all ingredients. Shake and serve in a cocktail glass.</string>
    <string name="ingredientesWhisky_CafeIrlandes">1 1/2 ounce of Irish Whiskey.\n6 ounces of hot black coffee.\nWhipped cream.\n3/4 oz Irish Cream
</string>
    <string name="prepararWhisky_CafeIrlandes">Place the whiskey in a cup of coffee, then add the hot coffee and Irish cream. Add the whipped cream the top, and garnish with ground coffee beans or brown sugar.</string>
    <!--
        ****************RON****************
        -->
    <string name="ingredientesRon_CubaLibre">160ml rum.\n
15ml lemon juice.\n
2 lemon peel.\n
Cola drink.\n
Ice cubes.
</string>
    <string name="prepararRon_CubaLibre">Place in tall glasses cubes, pour the lemon juice and add the rum, complete with cola; add the shells after rubbing with them the rim of the glass</string>
    <string name="ingredientesRon_PinaColada">Ice.\n
45ml white rum.\n
35ml coconut cream.\n
Juice or pineapple juice.\n
Pineapple and cherry slice.
</string>
    <string name="prepararRon_PinaColada">Pour ice, white rum, coconut cream and fill with pineapple juice.
Stir the mixture well and strain into a glass.
Garnish with pineapple slice and cherry.
</string>
    <string name="ingredientesRon_Mojito">Ice.\n
1 tablespoon sugar.\n
10ml lime juice.\n
50ml white rum.\n
Gaseous (7UP, Sprite, Fanta Lemon).\n
Peppermint or mint.
</string>
    <string name="prepararRon_Mojito">Put the mint and sugar in the glass and crush with a mortar
Add ice, lime juice and rum
Fill the glass with the gas and remove
Garnish with lemon or a sprig of mint
</string>
    <string name="ingredientesRon_Daikiri">90ml rum blanco.\n40ml parts lemon juice.\n1 part of sugar</string>
    <string name="prepararRon_Daikiri">Mix all ingredients in a shaker with ice. Shake and serve in a cocktail glass. you can also combine with fruits you want. </string>

    <string name="ingredientesRon_BlueHawaiian">Coconut cream.\nBlue Curacao.\n
Pineapple juice.\n
.\nRon White.
</string>
    <string name="prepararRon_BlueHawaiian">Pour into a blender with crushed ice 1oz White Rum, Blue Curacao 1oz, 1oz 2oz Coconut Cream and Pineapple Juice. Mix at maximum speed for 10 seconds, serve in a tall glass and garnish with a pineapple and a cherry.</string>
    <!--
          ****************VODKA****************
          -->

    <string name="ingredientesVodka_WhiteRussian">20 ml coffee liqueur (Kahlua or Tia Maria for example).\n
50ml of vodka.\n
30ml cream or milk.\n
</string>
    <string name="prepararVodka_WhiteRussian">It is a simple cocktail shaker does not require and is presented in short glass. The first is to fill the glass with ice, then pour the coffee liqueur, vodka and finally the cream. If you do not like milk or cream you can try using soy milk or directly go to Black Russian.</string>
 <string name="ingredientesVodka_Moradito">Vodka.\n
Grape juice.\n
brown sugar.
</string>
    <string name="prepararVodka_Moradito">Mixtures somewhat of good quality vodka with liqueur or grape juice (if it is natural is better) a tablespoon of brown sugar;
 if you use vodka instead of tequila
He tastes great and is called 69
</string>
    <string name="ingredientesVodka_BloodyMary">40 ml. vodka.\n
75 grams of tomato juice.\n
15 ml lemon juice.\n
2 strokes (squirts) Worcestershire sauce.\n
2-3 drops of tabasco.\n
Salt and freshly ground black pepper.\n
3-4 ice cubes.\n
1 tablespoon sherry also does well (optional).
</string>
    <string name="prepararVodka_BloodyMary">Prepare the glass with ice.
Pour the vodka.
Add the lemon.
Season with salt and pepper.
Add the sauce and Tabasco.
Fill with tomato.
Garnish with celery and serve.
</string>
    <string name="ingredientesVodka_BlueberrySpritzer">1 1/2 ounces of lavender and honey simple syrup.\n2 ounces of cranberry vodka
\n4 -6 oz lime soda or sparkling water\n1/4 lemon juice, freshly squeezed
</string>
    <string name="prepararVodka_BlueberrySpritzer">1. Combine lavender honey syrup, vodka and ice in a shaker.\n
2. Stir to combine, and strain into a cocktail glass or a flute.\n
3. Cover with water or soda, and finish with a few drops of fresh lemon juice.
</string>
    <string name="ingredientesVodka_SexOnTheBeach">1 1/2 ounces vodka.\n
Peach schnapps 3/4 oz (liquor peach / peaches).\n
1 1/2 oz freshly squeezed orange juice.\n
1 1/2 oz cranberry juice.\n
Ice.\n
collins glass.\n
2 straws.\n
1 slice of orange (or lemon) to decorate.\n
1 red cherry for garnish.\n
</string>
    <string name="prepararVodka_SexOnTheBeach">pour the vodka, peach schnapps, orange juice and blueberries. With a bar spoon stir gently for 10 seconds, add a couple of straws and garnish with a slice of good fresh orange on the rim. Finally add a red cherry, this will help in the decoration and give a more sensual and aromatic to this cocktail so sophisticated touch</string>

    <!--
          ****************MEZCAL****************
          -->
<string name="ingredientesMezcal_Zignumocuilli">1 oz SILVER ZIGNUM.\n
1 oz chamoy.\n
1 oz tamarind concentrate.\n
Worm salt or chili powder to decorate.\n
Strips of cucumber for garnish.
</string>
    <string name="prepararMezcal_Zignumocuilli">In a shaker put ice to taste, then add the Zignum oz Silver Mezcal with the chamoy and tamarind mixture for 35 seconds. Strain into a glass previously cooled and frosted with salt worm, finally garnish with cucumber also covered with salt or chili powder worm.</string>
    <string name="ingredientesMezcal_HotPinneapple">2 ounces of Zignum reposed.\n
4 ounces of pineapple juice.\n
Lemon juice ¼ oz.\n
Pineapple tidbits.
</string>
    <string name="prepararMezcal_Hotpinneapple">1. In a separate mixing jug mezcal with pineapple juice.\n
2. Add the lemon juice.\n
3. Add ice.\n
4. Frost the glass where Tajin serve with sauce around.\n
5. Decorate with a slice of pineapple on a shore enchilada.\n
6. Serve
</string>
    <string name="ingredientesMezcal_Tunacuixe">1 ounce of mezcal Treat Sprat-Madrecuixe.\n
4 pieces of tuna.\n
1 ounce natural syrup.\n
1/2 ounce lemon juice.\n
2 ounces of mineral water.
</string>
    <string name="prepararMezcal_Tunacuixe">Crush the ingredients in a mixing glass (except mineral water). Add ice, shake and serve the content (double cast). In the glass with ice, fill with mineral water.</string>
    <string name="ingredientesMezcal_Sunset">Natural lemon juice 25 ml.\n
Orange juice 25 ml.\n
25 ml white gold mezcal.\n
1 tablespoon liquid honey.\n
Crushed ice.\n
1 spiral lemon (to decorate).\n
</string>
    <string name="prepararMezcal_Sunset">Hours before putting the cups in the freezer. Add white mezcal, lemon juice and orange juice and move. Pour honey into the cup, long before the ice. Enter the ice and decorate as desired</string>
    <string name="ingredientesMezcal_BlackMexcan">1 1/2 ounce white mezcal.\n
1 ounce coffee liqueur.\n
Ice cubes.
</string>
    <string name="prepararMezcal_BlackMexican">Pour both drinks in a cocktail glass filled with ice</string>
    <string name="reto">Challenges</string>
    <string name="corona">King\'s Cup</string>
    <string name="jugadores">Log the players</string>
    <string name="jugador">Player </string>
    <string name="aceptar">Continue</string>
    <string name="iniciareto">I want a challenge</string>
    <string-array name="retos">
        <item>if there is a woman at the party, you drink a sip, if not, act like woman for 15 minutes.</item>
        <item>jugador1, you have to invite a round to all the players</item>
        <item>jugador1, you must drink the drink of the people who is in you righ side</item>
        <item>jugador1 has to take a drink for each person playing.</item>
        <item>jugador1 has to talk like Chinese, until you are told you can talk normally.</item>
        <item>jugador1, each person you touch a hair will have to take a sip of your drink.( you have to touch it in a sexy way)</item>
        <item>jugador1, you have to speak as Spanish for 10 minutes.</item>
        <item>jugador1, put your drink on the floor and tries to lift it and drink it without using your hands, if you do not succeed, shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1, tell a joke or a funny story, those who laugh will drink one shot, if no one laughs, you have to drink</item>
        <item>begins by saying the name of a drink, for example "mojito", the player to your right must continue and so on until someone repeat any mistake or who do drink a shot.</item>
        <item>Among all players mentioned who believe: die first, will have the best girl/boy and will have the best car, and explain why each person chosen must drink a shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1, tell a story (can be true or false), when you finish,  the others must vote if it is true or not, those who are wrong drink a shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1, tell the player to your right to name a body part now as it did, for example, if "head" must remain glued said the head for the next 3 rounds, if unstuck shot.</item>
        <item>among all form a circle, overturn the floor and loudly count to 3, then raise your face and gaze into the eyes of another player, if both see each other, they have to drink until their glasses are empty</item>
        <item>jugador1, must prepare a drink with 4 edible ingredients which want to jugador2, if jugador2 doesn´t drink it, shot</item>
        <item>among all take an ice cube with his hand, the first player that quit shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1, other player will have to give 10 pieces of clothing and you must use extras to which you already have, you will remain so for the rest of the activity, if not shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1, tell jugador2 the name of a body part now as it did need to put your tongue in your body said, if you can not shot.</item>
        <item>tries to say the alphabet backwards if you\'re wrong shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1, thers should blindfold, now everyone will say your name and have to say who said it, if you\'re wrong shot.</item>
        <item>should eat a banana and sensually suggestive, should have no other food can use, if not shot.</item>
        <item>have to take any object and tell others about this object for 1 minute, do not have to be real information, if not last the full minute shot.</item>
        <item>you have to cover your eyes, as they have done so should describe in detail how dressed any of the partygoers, if it does shot.</item>
        <item>must mention 3 parts of the body with 3 letters, if not shot.</item>
        <item>has 30 seconds to say 15 words beginning with the letter "a", if it does shot.</item>
        <item>must give arguments because player the falls as well or like much, if not believe the shot.</item>
        <item>may not say "yes" or "no" for the rest of the game, others may try to make you lose the game at any time, whenever you say shot.</item>
        <item>should hold his nose with his right hand while grasping the right ear with his left hand, then exchanged, the left ear with his right hand and nose with his left hand. You must do this 10 times unerringly, if not shot.</item>
        <item>must name 10 countries with their capitals not know if shot.</item>
        <item>must name 10 names or last names with the letter that others choose, if not shot.</item>
        <item>refer to the name of at least 5 former presidents of your country, if it does shot.</item>
        <item>should answer "no" to all questions that will make others arguing that throughout the game, if not shot.</item>
        <item>among all review their purses or bags and who has the weirdest shot object.</item>
        <item>will have to shout "die" every any of the other participants say no, for the rest of the game, whenever you do not shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1, must make a phone prank to a business friend or relative, if the other person on the phonecall don\'t fall in the prank, shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1, make a circle and each will have to say a word, the next will have to repeat the word I said before and say another third say the 2 above and more and so on, take the first shot that mistake.</item>
        <item>jugador1 must say the numbers 1 through 30, but without mentioning the multiples of 3, if you\'re wrong shot, do it to make it to 30.</item>
        <item>they have to drink the Jugador1 drink\'s and pour a spoonful of sauce or chili on it, if jugador1 don\'t drink it, shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1 has to say a short sentence and who is on your right should continue with a phrase that rhymes and so on, such as "1-My mom gave me a shirt, 2-With I always go to church, 3-Y I wrinkle is very fast ... "which can not be shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1 must say the names and ages of all participants, if you do not know shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1 will blindfolded while others hide, you will have to look for 2 minutes for the object, if you dont found it, shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1 will have to spell the name of the other participants, if you put the wrong shot</item>
        <item>jugador1, using the letters of the alphabet, in order,you must appoint a person\'s name with each of the letters, if you\'re wrong shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1 must guess blindfolded and using only the mouth, which object is playing, if it does shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1 should sing happy birthday using only one vowel, to be chosen by others if wrong shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1 has to sing a song gargling, if nobody guesses shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1, from now on everything you say must rhyme, such as "It\'s my turn and I\'ll get drunk..." if something does not rhyme shot.</item>
        <item>must say a defect and a quality of each of the participants, if you do not succeed shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1, from now on everything you will be saying words only with the vowel "e", whenever you are wrong shot.</item>
        <item>Everybody drink 5 sips of your drinks</item>
        <item>jugador1, must leave the house or place the game and get a cup of sugar. You can not return to the game until you reach with sugar or shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1, must remove a garment to another player, the opposite sex using only the mouth, others indicate who, if it does shot, if no one shot all opposite sex.</item>
        <item>from now will be a T-Rex so you cannot take off the elbows of your body if you forget to do this shot.</item>
        <item>you must say a word, the next right one that starts with the same syllable with which ended the previous word. For example: “apple” “lemon”. Apple ends with "le" and lemon starts with "le", the first shot is confused.</item>
        <item>whenever someone mentions a word with the letter "a" should drink a shot.</item>
        <item>jugador1, you must whisper to Jugador2 a question, and jugador2 will answer a question screaming. (Example, "Who is the prettiest in this party?"), Now others must guess what the question was, if they fail shot.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="copareyAs">WATERFALL</string>
    <string name="coparey2">2 FOR U.</string>
    <string name="coparey3">3 FOR ME</string>
    <string name="coparey4">4 ON THE FLOOR</string>
    <string name="coparey5">5 FOR GUYS</string>
    <string name="coparey6">6 FOR CHICKS</string>
    <string name="coparey7">7 HEAVEN</string>
    <string name="coparey8">8 WITH MATE</string>
    <string name="coparey9">9 RHYME</string>
    <string name="coparey10">CATEGORIES</string>
    <string name="copareyj">MAKE A RULE</string>
    <string name="copareyq">QUESTION MASTER</string>
    <string name="copareyk">KING\'S CUP!!!</string>
    <string name="copareyReglas">
         King\'s cup is a drinking game that uses playing cards. The player must drink and dispense drinks based on cards drawn.
        Each card has a rule that is predetermined before the game starts. Many houses have their own variation of rules.\n

Ace: \nAce is waterfall. This starts with everyone chugging.
        Then the person who picked the card can stop whenever he/she wants.
        This allows the next person to stop when he/she wants and so on and so on.
        This version is classic because it does a great job of getting everyone plastered.
\nTwo:\n Two has and always will be the classic you.
        This means that whoever picks the 2 card gets to choose anybody they want in the game to drink.
\nThree:\nThree for me. Pick a 3 and you have to drink.
\nFour:\nFour on the floor, everybody has to point to the ground the last person to do it has to drink.
\nFive:\n Five for guys. Guys have to drink.

\nSix:\n Six for Chicks, girls have to drink.
\nSeven:\nSeven heaven. All players reach for the sky.
        The last person has to drink. Great card when people aren\'t paying attention or someone is too
        drunk to realize a seven was picked.
\nEight:\nEight is mate. The player who picks the card chooses another player to be their mate.
        This means when one of them drinks they both drink. Perfect for letting the fine girl across
        the table know you are interested.
\nNine:\nNine is called bust a rhyme. The simple version has the player who picked the card say a
        word and everybody has to say a word that rhymes with it. Say for example the word is bite.
        Other players would say fight, kite, tight, right, etc. This goes on until somebody cannot
        think of a word that rhymes.

\nTen:\nTen is categories. The player who picked the card chooses a category.
        Then everyone goes around and says something that fits in the category.
        Whoever cannot think of anything in the category has to drink.

        \nJack:\nMake a Rule. Player makes a rule that lasts the entire game and if broken the violator must drink
\nQueen:\nQuestion Master.Player who flips over a queen becomes the question master until the next queen is flipped over.
        This player can ask anybody at any time a question and if that player doesn\'t respond with
        a question to the asker or another player he must drink

\nKing:\nKing\'s Cup.Pour however much beer/liquor you want into the glass, the 4th king has to drink the cup.
    </string>
    <string name="jugar">PLAY</string>
    <string name="comojugar">HOW TO PLAY</string>
    <string name="jugardenuevo">Play again</string>
    <string name="salir">Exit</string>
    <string name="retosreglas">Easy, follow the instructions which showy every challenge...</string>
    <string name="fincorona">End of game</string>

    <string name="mensajealcohol">Please drink responsibly.
        By continuing, you agree you are responsable for any  \n consequences that may result \nusing Apparrandear app</string>
    <string name="precaucion">Caution</string>


    <string name="bannerinferior">ca-app-pub-8694874567384392/7292574665</string>
    <string name="bannerinf2">ca-app-pub-8694874567384392/8769307867</string>
    <string name="bannerinf3">ca-app-pub-8694874567384392/1246041065</string>
    <string name="bannerinf4">ca-app-pub-8694874567384392/2722774263</string>
    <string name="bannerinf5">ca-app-pub-8694874567384392/4199507461</string>
    <string name="bannerinf6">ca-app-pub-8694874567384392/4339108266</string>

 <string name="infoacercade">Version 1.0, developed for mobile devices with android 3.1 or higher.
The user is responsible for any incidents that may occur with the use of the application. The development team does not award the creation of images and fonts used.
     The commercialization of this application is forbidden.
     For more information contact us by mail alumnosITMorelia@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="continuar">Continue</string>
    <string name="agregar">Add</string>
    <string name="NombresRepetidos">Please, don\'t repeat names</string>
    <string name="NoNombres">You need to type at least two names</string>
    <string name="UnNombre">Type more than one name, don\'t be a Forever Alone</string>
</resources>





